Sea Beast is a horror, science fiction, tv movie film directed by Paul Ziller.
In the fishing village of Cedar Bay, terror lies within the water.
And now it has surfaced in search of something more
substantial to devour than marine life: human flesh.
A captain and a sea biologist must wage a terrifying battle against the
deadly creatures in order to save mankind from total extinction.
Will McKenna, played by Corin Nemec.
Carly McKenna, played by Miriam McDonald.
Arden, played by Camille Sullivan.
Erin, played by Christie Laing.
Sheriff Jay McKenna, played by Gary Hudson.
Danny, played by Daniel Wisler.
The Sea Beast may refer to:
The Sea Beast (1926 film), an American silent drama film
The Sea Beast (2022 film), an animated adventure film
The Sea Beast, a Creature from the Black Lagoon-esque monster and the antagonist of "Twenty
Thousand Screams Under the Sea", episode 9 of Scooby-Doo and Scrappy-Doo (1979)
"The Sea Beast", The Mighty Hercules season 3, episode 18 (1965)
The Sea Beast, a cancelled video game project from Don Bluth Entertainment
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and intense.